priest came and said, "Will you
show me the dead grandmother later?" But there's a
problem. There's one more thing to be
afraid of. This part is my grandfather's. There's one
thing here, this one that holds the broom.
Today, the process is holding, isn't it? There's a little bit of something
here.  Well, it had been cut
, the blade had become two pieces, it
was hanging like this from here, it was
always like this, it was
April, the owner said, where can I put it?   Do
n't talk about it.
Do it, as the Lord says.  I said the kitchen was a
one-room house, my brother entered the kitchen,
put a lot of coal, filled it with incense, entered the
vobshm body, started praying, started to
beat and my father said, "We are not alone, we do
not see anyone, there was smoke from the house,
one of my friends was doing this, an Armenian
film, that student did this, and the
sun was blowing from the sky,
a dry piece of wood came from the Armenian report,
now we were silent, then
my father opened the windows so that we could
not see that smoke, my grandmother's moment was lost, my
grandmother's moment, she took the opportunity
to use the opportunity, the officer was looking,
something was jumping, something was happening,
and Vahagn was my "Oh,
Vahagn, Vahagn, Vahagn, let's
go down, outside, outside, outside, there was something, there was
no law, there was a
table"  You were putting it on, spreading the carpet, bringing it,
and the people of the building took it, and the
dear audience watched, and we put
things like this, we destroyed
things, the people came down, those seven people came down with the
gnomes, we put them standing, and then my
eye fell on our window, Ani, and then
I see this Vahag, I had
given the camera to Vahag, he said, "Oh, my father
wanted two shots of something, and then I saw
my father open the window, do this,
hang from above, do these things, let me look,
what are you taking pictures of, and then he went down, and
now people
are already preparing to put it in a dream, that time it
was a dream, there were no limousines anymore, I
came and people are standing, that we have to
take this out, put it in a dream, I came to
say, "Look at him, look
The most cheerful
but I only tell you, oh
The most cheerful we
take to Byurakan, their village
Byurakan said, you will bury us, we take to
Byurakan, and during that
period, the thing was, brother, there was supposed to be a
concert of the Golden Autumn, at the time, they
did a concert like that in the stadium, and they did something else, and they were going to be frank. On
the dream, there is a poster of the Golden Autumn,
but on the face is a tattoo, and on the face
of the dream, there is a tattoo, and on the face of the dream, there is a tattoo, and on the side, there is a
horse,
[applause] they can
see you, who am I, you, he, he, my
grandmother, she was a little bit of a believer,
and she used to tell me, look at the moon, look at it, like that, they were
becoming wolves, did you notice,
looking at the thing?
Oh, maybe that was the reason, because she didn't say anything,
I don't know why, and because of that, as if she was getting
more scared, I was looking at
the moon, saying, don't look at what she was
saying, what she was saying, in front of her,
and
Then you say, don't look at your shadow, don't look at your shadow. He was
making you look
bad. Don't look at your walking. Don't look at your clothes. Look under your feet. That's how
I was formed. I'm still a believer in life.
So what's wrong with superstition? You're getting older at
night. It's not the house. We don't cut our
nails. I'm in the middle of a topic. Don't you cut your hair at night? I didn't cut my hair at night. I didn't cut my hair at night. We do
n't cut my hair at all.
For example, I didn't know that you can't
cut your hair at night. But I never cut my hair at night.
Try it today. Just do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. You don't have to do it. You don't have to do it.
You'll see what happens tomorrow.
And now there are situations like that. I've grown up,
but
that squeezing still remains. Let's